Sheet Music Collection UA064
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Sheet Music Collection
1900 -- 1920
1883 -- 1943
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Department of Music
UA064
3.45 Linear Feet 7 boxes
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series: Sheet Music Collection.
Biographical / Historical
The Department of Music was established on August 7, 1895 when the Tufts College Board of Trustees voted to create a professorship in the History and Theory of Music. Professor Leo R. Lewis was appointed to the new position. Interest in music at Tufts was high from the onset. In 1896 President Capen's annual report counted 26 students enrolled in music courses - nearly 10% of Tufts' 270 students. By 1901, the Department of Music was declared "permanent" by President Capen, who lauded Professor Lewis for creating a department "likely to become one of the strongest of the College." Capen also praised Lewis for creating a chorus for the Sunday evening services in Goddard Chapel, organizing and instructing the Glee Club, preparing college songs, and "awakening an interest in music throughout the College." (Hersey, p. 32)
Tufts Music Department has always played a major role in organizing musical performances on campus. Historically, performance groups included the Glee Club, the Tufts Choir, the Banjo Club (which became the Mandolin and Guitar Club), the Jackson Glee Club, the Orchestra, the Chamber Singers, and the College Band. By 2007 Tufts Music Department had expanded its vocal and instrumental groups to include 19 performance ensembles including the Chamber Singers, Concert Choir, Tufts Jazz Orchestra (TJO), Tufts Symphony Orchestra (TSO), Wind Ensemble, and Pep Band. The Department organizes over 180 events and concerts annually.
In 1899, the Music Department found its first official home on the third floor of Goddard Gymnasium. This original space consisted of two rooms; one for general use and a second for the Music Library, which housed the collections of Rev. Thomas Wittemore, Albert Metcalf, and Frederic Louis Ritter. In 1930, the Old Chemistry Lab on Boston Avenue was converted to the "Music House." The department remained there until 1955, when it moved to the basement of the newly built Edward E. Cohen Arts Center (now Aidekman Arts Center). Outgrowing its basement facilities, the music department was relocated to 20 Professors Row, which had appropriately been home to Professor Lewis throughout his 50 year career at Tufts. In 2005 the Department found an interim home on 48 Professors Row, before making its final move to the $27 million Granoff Music Center in 2007. The Center houses the Distiler Performance Hall, the Lily Music Library, three classrooms, 20 faculty offices, and a rehearsal hall.
As of 2010, Music remains one of the largest and most active academic departments on Tufts campus, offering courses in musicology, ethnomusicology, theory, composition, and performance. Each year around 1,500 Tufts students enroll in department classes. Since 1973 a reciprocal agreement with the New England Conservatory of Music (NEC) has allowed students at both institutions to take courses at either school to be applied toward their respective degrees. Tufts also offers a five year dual-degree program with NEC, giving students the opportunity to earn their B.A. or B.S. from Tufts while earning a Bachelor of Music from NEC.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains published sheet music by Tufts composers. Composers include faculty and students. The majority of the pieces are about Tufts or composed for Tufts events such as Class Day. Songs not related to Tufts but printed by the Tufts Press are also included.
Formats range from penny song cards with lyrics only to full scores with orchestral or band arrangements.
In the early part of the 20th century, Tufts had an active community of composers. Led by Leo Rich Lewis, A1887, H1922, both a graduate and faculty member at the college, a multitude of songs for and about Tufts were published. Lewis, composer of Tufts' Alma Mater, acted as a mentor for many students who wrote some of the most well-known Tufts songs, such as Tuftonia's Day, the fight song still performed today. This collection contains the published results of these efforts, music that was published for the most part by the Tufts College Press for sale to members of the Tufts community.
Alumni and Alumni Relations; Curriculum and Instruction -- Faculty; Curriculum and Instruction -- Student Work; Student Activities -- Performing Arts; Performing Arts
- Sheet music collection, 1883 -- 1943; 1900 -- 1920; UA064.001; 3.45 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains published sheet music by Tufts composers. Composers include faculty and students. In the early part of the 20th century, Tufts had an active community of composers. Led by Leo Rich Lewis, A1887, H1922, both a graduate and faculty member at the college, a multitude of songs for and about Tufts were published. Lewis, composer of Tufts' Alma Mater, acted as a mentor for many students who wrote some of the most well-known Tufts songs, such as Tuftonia's Day, the fight song still performed today. This series contains the published results of these efforts, music that was published for the most part by the Tufts College Press for sale to members of the Tufts community. Published sheet music by Tufts composers. Composers include faculty and students. The majority of the pieces are about Tufts or composed for Tufts events such as Class Day. Songs not related to Tufts but printed by the Tufts Press are also included.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged by material size, and then alphabetically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Alma Mater's Day [Full Orchestra], 1923; UA064.001.001.00001; Hayes, Elliott W.; Hayes, G.H. (Box 1)
    Parts; Music of Tufts College Serial No. 53
  - Alpha Xi Zeta, 1921; UA064.001.001.00002; Morse, E.S.; Hunt, R.S. (Box 1)
  - America the Beautiful [For Mixed Chorus], 1936; UA064.001.001.00003; Lewis, Leo Rich; Bates, Katherine Lee (Box 1)
    For Mixed Chorus; The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 267.
  - Aren't You Glad? [Full Band], 1921; UA064.001.001.00004; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
    Full Band; The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 14
  - Aren't You Glad? [Medium Orchestra], 1921; UA064.001.001.00005; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
    Medium Orchestra; The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 14
  - Aren't You Glad? [Unison, with Piano, C], 1920; UA064.001.001.00006; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
    Unison, with Piano, C.
  - Around the Rez, 1905; UA064.001.001.00007; Dustin, M.N. (Box 1)
    A Tufts Two-Step
  - Beloved America, 1918; UA064.001.001.00008; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Cards.
  - The Book of Tufts Music (selection), 1922; UA064.001.001.00009; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Tuftonia's Day; Tufts Today, Tufts for Aye; Fight, Tufts, Fight; The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 27.
  - Bow Down Thine Ear, 1908; UA064.001.001.00010; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
  - Brown and Blue [Medium Orchestra Arrangement], 1922; UA064.001.001.00011; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
    Medium Orchestra Arrangement; The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 4.
  - Brown and Blue [Parts], 1905; UA064.001.001.00012; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
    Parts
  - Brown and Blue [Full Band], 1921; UA064.001.001.00013; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
    Parts; Music of Tufts College Serial No. 4
  - Calm After a Storm, 1922; UA064.001.001.00014; Bullard, Carrie (Box 1)
  - Campus Song, 1898; UA064.001.001.00015; Smith, A.W. (Box 1)
    Title of Campus Song is 'Alma Mater Hail!'
  - Cavalier Songs [Bass or Baritone], 1913; UA064.001.001.00016; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 1)
    Bass or Baritone.
  - Charlie Refined Song, 1922; UA064.001.001.00017; Patterson, C.H. (Box 1)
  - Class Day [Full Band], 1920; UA064.001.001.00018; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Full Band; The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 51.
  - Class Song of 1886, UA064.001.001.00019; Whittemore, H.W. (Box 1)
  - Class Song of 1901, UA064.001.001.00020; Wright, Bertha Louise; Fuller, George Washington (Box 1)
  - Class Song of 1902, UA064.001.001.00021; Lyon, Blanche Elizabeth; Parker, Mary Bates (Box 1)
  - Class Song of 1904, UA064.001.001.00022; Harmon, Betsey Barker; Phillips, Ethel May (Box 1)
  - Class Song of 1906, UA064.001.001.00023; Lendall, Harry N.; Tenney, Miriam (Box 1)
  - Class Song of 1909, UA064.001.001.00024; Doane, Lewis; Bush, Reba May (Box 1)
  - Class Song of 1911, UA064.001.001.00025; Lamont, R.R.; Gott, Charles (Box 1)
  - Columbia's Emblem [C], 1893; UA064.001.001.00026; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    For Single Voice or Unison Chorus; In C.
  - Columbia's Emblem [D flat], 1893; UA064.001.001.00027; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    For Single Voice or Unison Chorus; In D-flat.
  - Columbia's Emblem [Song Sheet in C], 1893; UA064.001.001.00028; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Song Sheet in C.
  - Columbia's Emblem [Song Sheet in D-flat], 1893; UA064.001.001.00029; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Song Sheet in D-flat.
  - The Consolation of Music, 1894; UA064.001.001.00030; Lewis, Leo Rich; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 1)
  - The Consolation of Music [Revised Edition], 1941; UA064.001.001.00031; Lewis, Leo Rich; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 1)
    Tufts Music Series Number 248; Revised Edition.
  - Current Tufts Songs, 1930; UA064.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
    Tuftonia's Day; Brown and Blue; Dear Alma Mater; Tufts Today, Tufts for Aye; Fight, Tufts, Fight!, Loyalty (Jackson); Tribute to Alma Mater (Jackson); Spell it out for Tufts; Forward, Tufts!; That Mascot; Win for the Brown and Blue; That's Why; Chorus of Barnum Song
  - Dear Alma Mater, 1899; UA064.001.001.00033; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
  - Dear Alma Mater [Glee Club], 1899; UA064.001.001.00034; Lewis, Leo Rich; Maulsby, David Lee (Box 1)
    In C, with melody in first bass.
  - Dear Alma Mater [Medium Orchestra], 1899; UA064.001.001.00035; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    The Music of Tufts College Serial Numbers 9 and 18.
  - Dear Alma Mater, 1899; UA064.001.001.00036; Lewis, Leo Rich; Maulsby, David Lee (Box 1)
    For Unison Chorus.
  - Dear Chapel Bell, 1920; UA064.001.001.00037; Horne, Alexander; Cohen, Edward I. (Box 1)
    The Music of Tufts College.
  - A Dear Little Goose, 1909; UA064.001.001.00038; Bullard, Carrie (Box 1)
  - Dedication to the Bell, 1908; UA064.001.001.00039; Moore, Willis A. (Box 1)
  - Good Enuf to Eat, 1918; UA064.001.001.00040; Bullard, Carrie; Stevens, James S. (Box 1)
    For High Voice.
  - The Fairy Godmother's Lesson, 1912; UA064.001.001.00041; Bullard, Carrie; Lewis, Abbie Goodwin (Box 1)
  - Fealty [Class Song of 1914], UA064.001.001.00042; Macy, E. Hazel; MacKnight, Annette B. (Box 1)
  - Fifteen Songs of Tufts College, UA064.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
    Brown and Blue; Dear Alma Mater; Chorus of Barnum Song; Tufts Victory Song; Forward, Tufts!; Tuftonia's Day; Fight, Tufts, Fight!; Tribute to Alma Mater; Spell it out for Tufts; Tufts Today, Tufts for Aye; In Praise of Alma Mater; Song of the Awakening; That Mascot; Te Salutamus.
  - Fight [Full Band], 1930; UA064.001.001.00044; Hayes, Elliott W. (Box 1)
    The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 30.
  - Fight [Orchestral], 1930; UA064.001.001.00045; Hayes, Elliott W. (Box 1)
  - Fight, Boys, Fight [card], 1915; UA064.001.001.00046; Hayes, Elliott W.; Cutler, G.L. (Box 1)
    Card.
  - Fight, Boys, Fight [Full Band], 1918; UA064.001.001.00047; Hayes, Elliott W. (Box 1)
  - Fight, Tufts, Fight [Orchestral], 1918; UA064.001.001.00048; Hayes, Elliott W. (Box 1)
    Orchestral
  - Fight, Boys, Fight [Pennycard Series], 1918; UA064.001.001.00049; Hayes, Elliott W.; Cutler, G.L. (Box 1)
    Pennycard Series.
  - Football Song, 1922; UA064.001.001.00050; Hayes, Elliott W. (Box 1)
  - For Tufts Hurrah! [Complete Orchestra], 1922; UA064.001.001.00051; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Complete Orchestra.
  - Forward [card], 1918; UA064.001.001.00052; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
  - Forward [Chorus in A-flat], 1918; UA064.001.001.00053; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Pennycard Series; Chorus in A-flat.
  - Forward [Chorus in B-flat], 1918; UA064.001.001.00054; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Pennycard Series; Chorus in B-flat.
  - Forward [E-flat), 1918; UA064.001.001.00055; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    E-flat.
  - Forward. Tufts! [Full Band], 1910; UA064.001.001.00056; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Full Band; The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 24.
  - Forward, Tufts! [Male Chorus], 1910; UA064.001.001.00057; Lewis, Leo Rich; Maulsby, David Lee (Box 1)
    Male Chorus in G.
  - Forward [March with Song Trio], 1910; UA064.001.001.00058; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    March with Song Trio.
  - Forward, Tufts! [Medium Orchestra], 1927; UA064.001.001.00059; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Medium Orchestra.
  - Forward, Tufts! [Mixed Chorus in F], 1911; UA064.001.001.00060; Lewis, Leo Rich; Maulsby, David Lee (Box 1)
    Mixed Chorus in F; Voice Parts for Mixed Chorus.
  - Forward, Tufts! [Organ in E-flat], 1910; UA064.001.001.00061; Lewis, Leo Rich; Maulsby, David Lee (Box 1)
    Organ in E-flat.
  - Forward, Tufts! [Organ in F], 1911; UA064.001.001.00062; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Organ in F.
  - Forward, Tufts! [Piano, four hands, in F], 1911; UA064.001.001.00063; Lewis, Leo Rich; Maulsby, David Lee (Box 1)
    Piano in F.
  - Forward, Tufts! [Piano, two hands in E-flat], 1911; UA064.001.001.00064; Lewis, Leo Rich; Maulsby, David Lee (Box 1)
    Piano in E-flat.
  - Forward, Tufts! [Voice parts for Glee Club], 1908; UA064.001.001.00065; Lewis, Leo Rich; Maulsby, David Lee (Box 1)
    Voice Parts for Glee Club.
  - Fughetta Gehasonia, 1930; UA064.001.001.00066; Chakmakjian, Alan Vaness (Box 1)
    The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 75; Piano Solo.
  - Guard Old Glory, 1918; UA064.001.001.00067; Lewis, Leo Rich; Earle, John Henry (Box 1)
    Pennycard Series; cards.
  - He That Dwelleth in the Secret Place, 1911; UA064.001.001.00068; Bullard, Carrie (Box 1)
    For mixed voices.
  - Hill Song [Class Song of 1927], UA064.001.001.00069; Boyden, Louise Emilie; Lowe, Miriam (Box 1)
    Class Song of 1927.
  - Hymn to College Hill, 1935; UA064.001.001.00070; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
    For Tufts Hurrah; Dear Alma Mater; We Love it for Aye; Tuftonia's Day; Aren't You Glad You Are a Tufts Man?; Fight, Tufts, Fight; Forward, Tufts!.
  - In Memoriam [Parts], 1940; UA064.001.001.00071 (Box 1)
    Parts; Bass; Cello; Viola; Violin I and II.
  - In Praise of Alma Mater, 1920; UA064.001.001.00072; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Song-Trio of March "Class Day".
  - The Interviewer [Reporter], 1883; UA064.001.001.00073; Lewis, Abbie Goodwin; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Reporter.
  - Jack and the Baked Bean Stalk, 1909; UA064.001.001.00074; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 1)
    Cantata.
  - Jumbo Cantepic, UA064.001.001.00075; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
  - Jumbo the Great, 1922; UA064.001.001.00076; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
  - Jumbo the Great [Chorus], 1922; UA064.001.001.00077; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Chorus.
  - Jumbo the Great [Glee Club Parts], 1922; UA064.001.001.00078; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Sopranos and Altos.
  - Jumbo Song [1922- Autographed], UA064.001.001.00079; Garabedian, Carl A. (Box 1)
    Autographed by Carl A. Garabedian.
  - Kapp Gamma Psi, 1926; UA064.001.001.00080; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
  - The Land We Love the Best [card], 1918; UA064.001.001.00081; Lewis, Leo Rich; Waterman, Nixon (Box 1)
  - The Land We Love the Best [For Solo & Chorus in F], 1914; UA064.001.001.00082; Lewis, Leo Rich; Waterman, Nixon (Box 1)
    For Solo and Chorus in F.
  - The Land We Love the Best [For Unison Singing], 1914; UA064.001.001.00083; Lewis, Leo Rich; Waterman, Nixon (Box 1)
    For Unison Singing.
  - The Land We Love the Best [Full, F, 16mo], 1914; UA064.001.001.00084; Lewis, Leo Rich; Waterman, Nixon (Box 1)
    Full, F, 16mo.
  - The Land We Love the Best [unlabelled version], 1914; UA064.001.001.00085; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Unlabelled.
  - The land we love the best [Voice parts with text], 1914; UA064.001.001.00086; Lewis, Leo Rich; Waterman, Nixon (Box 1)
    Voice parts with text.
  - Lena, 1888; UA064.001.001.00087; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Song for Male Chorus with Tenor Solo.
  - Lightnin!, 1933; UA064.001.001.00088; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 80.
  - Like Bending Barley, 1933; UA064.001.001.00089; Lewis, Leo Rich; Teasdale, Sara (Box 1)
  - Lincoln Day Program, 1909; UA064.001.001.00090; Lewis, Leo Rich; Bullard, Carrie (Box 1)
    Laus Deo; The Death of Lincoln; Homage to Lincoln; Sail On, O Ship of State.
  - Loyalty [card], 1912; UA064.001.001.00091; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
  - Loyalty [Full Band Parts], 1912; UA064.001.001.00092; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Full Band Parts; The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 293.
  - Loyalty [Pennycard Series], 1912; UA064.001.001.00093; Lewis, Leo Rich; Adams, Gladys Marion (Box 1)
    A Song of Women in War Time.
  - Loyalty [Song Book], 1912; UA064.001.001.00094; Lewis, Leo Rich; Adams, Gladys Marion (Box 1)
    A Song of Jackson College.
  - March Old Powderhouse [Full Band Arrangement], 1928; UA064.001.001.00095; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 73; Full Band Arrangement.
  - May-Time [Maitag], 1895; UA064.001.001.00096; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Maitag; Part-Song for Mixed Chorus.
  - Medley Fantasia on Tufts Airs [Organ], 1935; UA064.001.001.00097; Morton, J.W. (Box 1)
    Tufts Night at the Symphony Hall, May 21, 1913; Organ.
  - The Moo Cow Moo, 1913; UA064.001.001.00098; Bullard, Carrie (Box 1)
    Children Song.
  - The Moo Cow Moo [Glee Club], 1916; UA064.001.001.00099; Bullard, Carrie (Box 1)
    Glee Club Parts.
  - The Music of Tufts College [compilation], 1895; UA064.001.001.00100; Lewis, Leo Rich; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
    Barnum Song; We Love it for Aye; For Tufts Hurrah; Brown and Blue; Hymn to College Hill.
  - Music of Tufts College [compilation], UA064.001.001.00101; Newton, E.W.; Marshall, Donald Leslie; Goldshine, Meriam; Morison, Norman W.; Lamont, R.R.; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Class Song of 1921; Charlie Tufts Hurrah!; Charlie's Light; Song of the Awakening; Spirit of Tufts; Alma Mater, at Thy Side; Guide of Our Youth.
  - The Music of Tufts College [compilation], UA064.001.001.00102; Lewis, Leo Rich; Bullard, Carrie; Wells, Chas H. (Box 1)
    Dago Man; When Hearts Are Young; Dear Alma Mater; Charlie Tufts, His College.
  - The Music of Tufts College [compilation], UA064.001.001.00103; Lewis, Leo Rich; Morton, J.W. (Box 1)
    Forward; Medley-Fantasia.
  - The Music of Tufts College [compilation], UA064.001.001.00104; Bullard, Carrie; Brooks, J. Bradford; Lewis, Leo Rich; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
    Gym Two Step; I've Been Thinking; Hullaballoo; Aren't You Glad; Tufts College Two-Step.
  - The Music of Tufts College [compilation], UA064.001.001.00105; Lewis, Leo Rich; Dow, Frank E.; Fisher, A.W.; Mulvey, E.C. (Box 1)
    Hail, Tufts!; Cheer for the Team; Pax et Lux; Victory Song; Loyalty.
  - The Music of Tufts College [compilation], UA064.001.001.00106; Lewis, Leo Rich; Hayes, Elliott W.; Williams, Allton T. (Box 1)
    Shell Out; Spell it Out; Class Day; In Praise of Alma Mater; Brown & Blue Forever.
  - The Music of Tufts College [compilation], UA064.001.001.00107; Hayes, Elliott W.; Rose, W.W.; Garabedian, Carl A.; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Tuftonia's Day; Voice of Alma Mater; Bodun Song; Fight.
  - The Music of Tufts College (compilation), UA064.001.001.00108; Lewis, Leo Rich; Merrill, M. H.; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
    Under Our Own Steam; Where to go to; For He's a Thoroughbred; Freshmen's Lament.
  - The Music of Tufts College [compilation], UA064.001.001.00109; Lewis, Leo Rich; Horne, Alexander (Box 1)
    We Stand; North and South; O Cherished Homeland; Guard Old Glory; Dear Chapel Bell; Beloved America.
  - A Night Song, 1927; UA064.001.001.00110; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
  - The Nobody Man, 1918; UA064.001.001.00111; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 1)
    Children's Song.
  - North and South [card], 1918; UA064.001.001.00112; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
  - North and South [Full Band], 1918; UA064.001.001.00113; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Full Band.
  - North and South [Unison Edition], 1918; UA064.001.001.00114; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Unison Edition.
  - O Cherished Homeland, 1918; UA064.001.001.00115; Lewis, Leo Rich; Maulsby, David Lee (Box 1)
    Card; Pennysheet Collection.
  - O Cherished Homeland [Mixed Chorus Parts with Text], 1918; UA064.001.001.00116; Lewis, Leo Rich; Maulsby, David Lee (Box 1)
    Mixed Chorus Parts with Text.
  - O Cherished Homeland [Unison, B-flat], 1918; UA064.001.001.00117; Lewis, Leo Rich; Maulsby, David Lee (Box 1)
    Unison; B-flat.
  - An Offring We Offer, UA064.001.001.00118; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 1)
    Netherlandish Folksong.
  - An Old-Time Celebration [Full Band], 1923; UA064.001.001.00119; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
    The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 36; Full Band.
  - Onward, Comrades!, 1910; UA064.001.001.00120; Lewis, Leo Rich; Maulsby, David Lee (Box 1)
  - Onward Still [Class Song of 1932], UA064.001.001.00121; MacPherson, Olive Beatrice (Box 1)
    Class Song of 1932.
  - Our Symbol [Class Song of 1940], UA064.001.001.00122; Lybeck, Phyllis (Box 1)
    Class Song of Tufts College, 1940.
  - Parent of Light [Class Song 1915], UA064.001.001.00123; Brooks, William Gooch (Box 1)
    Class Song of 1915.
  - Recessional, UA064.001.001.00124; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 1)
  - Rejoice, O Ye Righteous, 1911; UA064.001.001.00125; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Published for the Reunion Concert, May 17, 1911.
  - Remembrance [For Strings], 1933; UA064.001.001.00126; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
  - Ring Forth [Class Song 1926], UA064.001.001.00127; Wood, Edgar J. (Box 1)
  - Rollicking Road, 1932; UA064.001.001.00128; Bullard, Carrie (Box 1)
  - The Runaway, 1913; UA064.001.001.00129; Bullard, Carrie (Box 1)
  - Second String Quartet, 1940; UA064.001.001.00130; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
  - Seven Songs of Tufts College, 1936; UA064.001.001.00131; Newton, E.W. (Box 1)
    Tufts Night at the Pops, June 11, 1936; Brown and Blue; Dear Alma Mater; Tuftonia's Day; Spell it Out For Tufts; That Mascot; Forward, Tufts!; Fight, Tufts, Fight!.
  - Shell Out, 1920; UA064.001.001.00132; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Published by the Tufts Bookstore.
  - A Sky Voyage, 1917; UA064.001.001.00133; Bullard, Carrie (Box 1)
  - A Song of Fellowship, 1926; UA064.001.001.00134; Gaul, Harvey B. (Box 1)
    Part Song for Men's Voices.
  - Song of the Awakening, 1936; UA064.001.001.00135; Lamont, R.R. (Box 1)
    The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 57.
  - Sons of Goddard, 1913; UA064.001.001.00136; Newton, E.W.; Lamont, R.R. (Box 1)
    A Song of Goddard Seminary.
  - Spell it Out [Full-Band], 1922; UA064.001.001.00137; Williams, Allton T. (Box 1)
    The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 50.
  - Spell it Out [Medium Orchestra Arrangement], 1921; UA064.001.001.00138; Williams, Allton T. (Box 1)
  - Spell it Out for Tufts, 1920; UA064.001.001.00139; Williams, Allton T. (Box 1)
  - Spirit of Tufts, class song of 1916, UA064.001.001.00140 (Box 1)
  - The Sword of Ferrera, 1899; UA064.001.001.00141; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 1)
    B-flat.
  - Te Salatamos [Full Orchestra], 1939; UA064.001.001.00142; MacKillop Jr., Kenneth (Box 1)
    Full Orchestra.
  - Te Salutamus [Card], 1935; UA064.001.001.00143 (Box 1)
    Class Song of 1935
  - That Mascot, 1923; UA064.001.001.00144; Lewis, P. B. (Box 1)
    The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 66.
  - That Mascot [Full Band Arrangement], 1923; UA064.001.001.00145; Lewis, P. B. (Box 1)
  - That's Why [Full Band], 1939; UA064.001.001.00146; Bean, Norman S. (Box 1)
    Full Band Arrangement; The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 213.